export default {
    title: 'English Phrases | Inglês-Português',
    description: 'Flashcards com diversas frases em inglês para treinar a tradução para o português.',
    cards: [
        {
            front: "I've never done that.",
            back: "Eu nunca fiz isso."
        },
        {
            front: "This is my mother.",
            back: "Esta é minha mãe."
        },
        {
            front: "What school did you go to?",
            back: "Para qual escola você foi?"
        },
        {
            front: "Is your father home?",
            back: "O teu pai está em casa?"
        },
        {
            front: "When does it arrive?",
            back: "Quando ele chega?"
        },
        {
            front: "Should I wait?",
            back: "Eu deveria esperar?"
        },
        {
            front: "Is there any mail for me?",
            back: "Há alguma carta para mim?"
        },
        {
            front: "I've never done that.",
            back: "Eu nunca fiz isso."
        },
        {
            front: "May I speak to Mrs. Smith please?",
            back: "Eu posso falar com a Senhora Smith, por favor?"
        },
        {
            front: "What day of the week is it?",
            back: "Qual dia da semana é?"
        },
        {
            front: "We like it very much.",
            back: "Nós gostamos muito disso."
        },
        {
            front: "That looks great.",
            back: "Isso parace ótimo."
        },
        {
            front: "You're smarter than him.",
            back: "Você é mais inteligente do que ele."
        },
        {
            front: "It's a quarter to 7.",
            back: "É 15 para às 7."
        },
        {
            front: "Is there an English speaking guide?",
            back: "Tem algum guia que fale inglês?"
        },
        {
            front: "My grandmother passed away last year.",
            back: "Minha avó faleceu no ano passado."
        },
        {
            front: "I'm sorry, we're sold out.",
            back: "Me desculpe, estamos esgostado."
        },
        {
            front: "I've been there.",
            back: "Eu já estive lá."
        },
        {
            front: "Could you hand me a towel please?",
            back: "Você poderia me entregar uma toalha por favor?"
        },
        {
            front: "There's a restaurant over there, but I don't think it's very good.",
            back: "Há um restaurante lá, mas não acho muito bom."
        }
    ]
};